The End
What are you doing, Kaguya?
I'm joining you tonight.
You adore sharing your bed with ladies according to my kinswoman.
Your kinswoman?
What? Yusuru?
Implementation. According to my master, this is the best method to get rid of sweat.
Your master? Stop that, Kaguya!
Wait, you mean that you don't want me?
Why would she need to lick him in order to get off sweat?
You obviously do not know anything.
Understood.
My master said in order to warm you up properly,
I would need to have skin-to-skin contact with you.
Hey, what are you snuggling up to him like that for?
Ignore, this action is none of your business.
The space under the blanket belongs to adults.
What? Don't you underestimate me!
Oh, yeah.
Now, Shido, isn't this much warmer than what she was doing?
After all, Yuzuru gets cold so easily.
Negative. Since Kaguya's chest is lonelier,
she cannot produce very much heat at all.
What did you just say?
Hold it!
I will take care of Shido when he's not feeling well.
Let go. Shido is waiting for me right now.
Oh, my God, wait.
We're here, guys.
We can decide this thing for you.
This is Adeptus One.
I can confirm that the target has entered the room.
Roger.
Shall we deploy the Bandersnatch?
Have three units outside the room just in case they're needed.
Know that Master Sergeant Tobeichi is in there, too.
Make sure that the range of territory...
Did the target notice me?
Ellen?
Where in the world did you come from?
No!
Stop moving!
It's hard to address you!
Agreed.
You're acting like a little baby for a night-night.
Everyone is so energetic tonight.
I suppose there's no harm in letting them have their fun until light's out.
Shido, I heard that you were sleeping because you had a fever.
Are you okay?
Leave me alone!
Hey, hey, hey, come!
The school trip.
The children are permitted to buy wooden swords and then go to the girls' rooms.
They worry about getting caught by the teacher and wind up falling asleep on a quiet bus the
next day because no one got enough sleep.
That single moment can twinkle for a lifetime.
The children are permitted to buy wooden swords and then go to the girls' rooms.
The children are permitted to buy wooden swords and then go to the girls' room to buy wooden swords and then go to the girls' room.
It's the first time I'd like to be here
I'd like to meet you
I'd like to believe in that life
Not since earlier, sir
There's no movement within the building either
Bring the Bandersnatch back then
Nothing is going to happen tonight
Sir
And that little girl
All right
Let's review the plan
Okay
We'll have the spirit berserk
That is to say the Yamai sisters Kaguya and Yuzuru
Spend today's free time with you at the private beach
Where you are currently waiting
I'll tell them what to do
I've given them intercoms to make that happen
The rest is up to you, Shin
Got it
From there, I just, like, pretend I don't know about them
And let them win me over?
Yes, exactly
If they understand and believe that all they have to do
To make you fall for them is follow my directions
I'll be able to control their actions to some extent
At least that's the idea
In other words
As long as everything goes the way you think
There's a chance we could seal both of them at the same time
Correct
Judging by the girl's current dynamic
If you kiss one of them
There's no way to know how the other one will react
But the assumption is it won't be positive
Communications with Fraxinus have not yet been restored
However, if we do not seal the elusive Yamai sisters now
We may never get a second chance
So we have to make our move
You realize there are many risks involved
Yes, I understand
I'll do what I can to seal them without any fighting
Thus, Yuzuru or I will become the new Yamai
For there can be only one
What happens to the personality that loses?
It will cease to exist
I'll try my hardest
I'm scared I won't be able to do it though
I believe in you
They're almost done changing
In order to avoid confusion
I'm going to cut this line of communication for now
Don't forget to compliment them on their swimsuits
Aha, so this is where you've been hiding out, Shido
Discovery, I have finally found you, Shido
Oh, hey there, ladies
How are you doing?
Those swimsuits are incredible
You both look very pretty
Yeah, you better believe it
Acknowledge
Thank you for saying such kind words
Right, understood and on it
Duly noted
I understand as well
Hey, Shido
I demand you apply divine protection
From the miasma of light on my body
Request, will you please put sunblock onto me?
Um, sunblock?
Oh, it's a chore to work up much enthusiasm
When there's nothing to do
I did what cannot be undone
And it counted on a good abusive scolding
From the commander
And yet here I am, unabused and alone
And as expected, he's useless
If only analyst Murasame were here instead of that
Well, maybe we should try contacting her later
This is steamy
Way steamy
Now, Shido
I am turning my back to you with full trust
Don't let me down
Request, please do this for me
Yeah, sure thing
Let me take a wild kiss
This means I have to touch them directly, doesn't it?
Hey, Shido's not applying it
That is not what you said would happen
Inquiry
What am I doing incorrectly?
Um, okay, here I come
Okay, Shido
Now, put that protection on my back
Negligence
Didn't you hear me?
Jeez
Crap, I'm sorry
That was cold, wasn't it?
No, I'm perfectly fine
Keep going
Don't stop
Whatever you say
Counterattack
I saw an opening
Petition
Apply
Hurry and do me
Please, Shido
Right
I'm on it
Wow
Cold
Oh, my
You okay?
Wonderful
Oh, yes
You are very good at that
Thank you
No fair
I get to be next
Counterattack
I will not allow it
Oh, yeah?
What are you going to do?
I guess that I'll...
Um, are you two all right?
He doesn't know how good he is at all
Tremble, godlike fingers
He's such a wolf
A wolf
A wolf?
What?
Arbitel
The target is now on the move
Can you follow her?
She seems to be heading to a private beach
Point eight kilometers northwest of your current location
Then I will head that direction
Please have the Bandersnatch follow
Oh, my god, we so got you, Alan
Why would you do that?
Because!
It's never not hilarious
I can't believe we got you again
That's so lame
I'm sorry
I don't have time to play around
I have to go
Whatever, girl
And since you're already there
I know you must think it's fate that we've been buried here together like this
But I already have a phone, girlfriend
But with being all buried and everything
I can't exactly bring her out to show you
I understand
It's simply a coincidence that you guys are out here all by your lonesome
You bet
That's what happened for sure
Mm-hmm
Yes, that's my kinswoman Toka
Hastening right to her master's side
Very nicely done
Good work
Wonder
I did not think Master Origami would ever come to a place like this
Kinswoman?
Master?
Yes, she seemed to have a bright future
So we performed a baptism of darkness yesterday and exchanged bonds
Explanation
I was moved by Master's cockatry
I then asked to be her disciple
Right
I get it now
Moving on
What were the three of you doing together?
Uh, well, that's a funny story, actually
I thought we could play a little beach volleyball
Reina
Why did you show up like that?
I'm confused
Since Toka and Origami are here, we needed to change the original plan we had discussed
Now you, Kaguya, and Yuzuru will strengthen your bonds by playing on the same team and working together
Gregor, Jackson, and Spencer are on this side
Alexander, Abraham, and Anthony are on the other court
What's she talking about?
I wonder if this will work
I don't think Kaguya and Yuzuru will do well together
For that matter, neither will Toka nor Origami
Don't worry about that
I told them that I would tell the winning team an embarrassing secret about you
So they have the incentive to work with each other
Even if they don't want to
Why would you do that?
What are you doing, Yuzuru?
Rebuttal
That's my line
Don't get in my way, Kaguya
What do you mean?
You're in my territory
Don't overstep your bounds
Rebuttal
I didn't think dim-witted Kaguya would make it in time
What did you say to me?
Hey, calm down, girls
Calm down
All they do is fight
I don't think they're going to be very difficult to defeat
I'm disappointed
They don't know their place if they think they can beat us while acting like that
Well, Yuzuru
Shall we?
Agreement
Let's do it
Nice, Shido
Kaguya, set up now
Understood
Alright, did you see that?
Yeah
That was perfect just now, wasn't it, Yuzuru?
It went whiz, whiz
Affirmative
That's my Kaguya
No, no
That's my Yuzuru
I mean
Don't get too excited, Peon
You should be grateful that I allowed my feet to step on you
Nasty
Now my hands are extremely smelly
They stink
You know what it reminds me of?
The smells of old, dried, and fermented fish
My feet don't smell like that
Shin, are you alright?
Yeah, I guess so
But I'm starting to think this won't work
Honestly, so am I
Shido?
Kaguya?
There's, um, there's something I want to talk to you about
Is that okay?
Yeah, sure
Hey, Reina
Are you still telling the girls what to do?
No, I didn't say anything to either one
I just...
I wanted to say that, uh...
Uh, why are you talking normal?
Ah!
Uh, ha!
So you were taken in by my little farce, were you not?
Do you realize how ridiculous you looked?
Dancing in the palm of my hand like a fool?
Hey, don't look at me like that
I can't help the way I talk
This is normal for me, you know?
Funny, because you stopped doing it again
Ugh
Well, yeah
Since I am a spirit
I'm super amazing
And I gotta sound like I can wield a bunch of power and stuff
Like, how is that not obvious to you?
Seriously?
Whatever
It's annoying
So I'm changing it
Now, tomorrow
You have to choose me or Yuzuru, right?
You know
To decide our battle
Oh
Yeah
Shido
I want you to choose Yuzuru and not me
Huh?
Petition
Shido
Please choose Kaguya to win this match instead of me
But why?
Explanation
It is because Kaguya is so much better than I could ever hope to be
Surely you must realize how incredibly lovely she is
I mean, Yuzuru is super cute, right?
She's not like overly friendly or anything
But she does mean well
Her boobs are huge
And she's like a moe character come to life
She likes to act as though she is extremely strong
And the truth of the matter is that she's in earnest
Even so, she still looks like one touch will break her
And I'm sure holding that body can only be described as heavenly
But... then... but then you'll...
Of course
I'll disappear
I don't understand
Oh, come on
It's not like I want to disappear
But to me, there's something more important
I want Yuzuru to get to live
Desire
I want Kaguya to get to live
I want her to see and experience more of this world
You know I'm right
Kaguya is the spirit most suitable to be the true Yamai
I decided on a battle of charm because...
Well, because no matter how you look at it, Yuzuru is cuter
Certainly
No matter how you look at it, Kaguya is the cuter one
I only accepted the battle of charm because I knew she would win over me
Reminder
Shido, you have to choose Kaguya tomorrow
If you do not...
Then I'll attack this whole island and your friends who are on it
I'll blow them all away
Well, that was unexpected
I sense no ulterior motive behind what they said
This must actually be how they feel
To wish for her own disappearance so that the other one can live
What the hell is going on?
Shido, I want you to choose Yuzuru and not me
Petition
Shido, please choose Kaguya to win this match instead of me
Shido?
Shido!
Toka
You finally heard me
I was calling out for you this whole time
Sorry about that
Hey, Shido
Do you maybe want to go see the ocean at night?
Analyst Murasame, please respond
This is Fraxinus
Analyst Murasame
It's no use
I can't get through
I can't get through to Shido's line either
That's strange
Looking at these readings
I doubt it's as simple as a transmission malfunction
Artificial interference
Then who could be responsible?
Hey guys, what's going on?
Arbito, can you see her?
The target is currently on the move along the coast with a male student
I will now commence the attack
Roger that
Also, have a bandersnatch on standby
As close to the hotel as possible
I'm concerned about Master Sergeant Tobeichi
We can't afford for her to see any suspicious movements
Sorry, Shido
Huh?
What for?
When I said I wanted to go for a walk to see the ocean at night
It was kind of a little lie
Even though we came on this school trip together
I don't feel like
Like we've been able to talk that much
And so
I wanted some time alone
Just the two of us, if that's okay
But if you're angry, I understand
Anyway, Shido
What happened earlier?
What?
What do you mean?
I don't know why
But I feel like you've been worried about something recently
But, uh
If it's nothing, then that's great
Tell me, Toka
Did you bring me out here just because you were worried?
Yeah
Well, I guess not entirely
I still wanted some alone time
You can't blame me for that
Toka, can I ask for your advice?
Sure
By all means, ask away
Bandersnatch, deployment complete
Captain
We have reports of a mysterious source intermittently communicating with a Ruby Island, sir
We do?
I believe it's trying different patterns in an attempt to get around the interference
Hmm
Seriously?
Like, Kaguya and Yuzuru do?
That's right
They both separately told me they want the other to live
Even if that means they will no longer exist
It's weird
As much as they argue
I never thought they felt that way about each other
Well, who would've?
Though, I must say
I understand it
If I were told that if I didn't die, you would
Then I'd probably do the same
Toka
Uh, just forget I said that
Please continue
Okay
So then, now that I've been told that
What do you think I should do about this?
What are you talking about?
Kaguya!
Yuzuru?
I don't buy that
It doesn't make any sense
Hold on
Just calm down
Demand
Repeat
Yuzuru?
Kaguya
She told you to choose me?
Is that really what she said?
Uh-oh
They look mad
Please, girls
You have to listen to me
What the hell?
Raphael!
Hurry up!
Respond
Raphael!
El Nahar!
A territory has been deployed
What's going on?
Uragami Tobiichi
What are you doing out here?
Miss Murasami!
Run away!
I see
It's a little dangerous
But let's send personnel
To communicate directly
Bring us to 1,000 meters
Above ground level
Deploy the Yggdropholium
Yes!
On it, sir!
Approaching target coordinates
No reaction
To the permanent territory
Very well
Now
Ready the Yggdropholium
Deploy!
Captain, the radar's picking up something
Is it an aircraft?
No, wait a sec
Sir, it's an airship
The signal's gone
The Ratatasker organization
When you see that ship again
I want it taken down
Fire at will
Yes, this is my lucky day
Prepare the main artillery
At Ashcroft beta devices
10 through 20
Start producing magical power
Our target is a warship
Of unknown affiliation
So what the hell was all that about, huh?
A joke?
Why tell him to choose me?
Rebuttal
What about you?
What is your intention?
It's no use
I thought this method
Would give us the chance
To finally decide fair and square
But I guess that I must have forgotten
To add your idiocy
Into the equation
Agreement
I cannot take any more
Of your immense stupidity either
Perhaps it was asking too much
To have someone else
In a duel we started ourselves
After all
Look where we've ended up
Looks like we're gonna have
To take care of it ourselves
No matter what
The dueling method is?
Naturally
I already know
Whoever falls first
Is the winner
No, they have to stop
Please stop
It's a journey
To save you
The story
It's a journey
So
Sometimes
It's going to govern
You're not
The future
But when you were
When you are
Come here
I'll talk
Not for a program
It's a journey
I'll see you next time.